sunny.co.uk 2015-03-17

# Privacy Policy - Sunny

Your personal information 

Elevate Credit International Limited is committed to respecting and protecting your privacy and ensuring that all of the information we hold about you is correct, relevant and secure. We abide by the Data Protection Act 1998 and are registered as Data Controllers with the Information Commissioner's Office. 

Use of your information 

By using this website you agree to Elevate Credit International Limited holding and processing your personal and non-personal information for the following purposes to: 

  * Manage your account
  * Make decisions regarding your identity and whether to make further cash available for you to borrow.
  * Undertake periodic statistical analysis or testing to ensure the accuracy of existing and future products and services.
  * Recover debt.
  * Prevent and detect crime.
  * Understand our customers' requirements and provide better services.
  * Develop, improve and test products and services.

We do not disclose your information to any other person **except** : 

  * To credit reference and fraud prevention agencies and other service companies.
  * To government entities or regulatory bodies as required by law.
  * To sub-contractors who work on our behalf.
  * To anyone we have appointed for administration of this agreement.
  * To anyone we have appointed for debt collection purposes.
  * In the event we sell or otherwise transfer this agreement.

We do not disclose your information to any other person **unless** : 

  * We have your permission.
  * We are required or permitted to do so by law.

Where we store your personal information 

All of your information is stored on our secure servers, and is reviewed on a regular basis to ensure that it remains up-to-date and relevant. We will not retain your personal information for any longer than necessary in line with our Data Protection Act obligations. 

Countries within the European Economic Area (EEA) are required to have a similar standard of protection of personal data. We may transfer personal data outside the EEA but will ensure that before we do so, there is adequate protection as required by the relevant Data Protection legislation. 

Elevate Credit International Limited is owned by Elevate Credit, Inc., a company based in the USA. From time to time customer data will be securely transmitted to, or our systems accessed by, Elevate Credit, Inc. in order to analyse our data and provide audit services. Elevate Credit, Inc., is certified under the US Safe Harbor Privacy Principles, which ensure that any data transmitted to, or accessed by it, will be used and managed in a way that is as safe, secure and appropriate. To view the full Elevate Credit, Inc., Safe Harbor Privacy Policy click [here](http://www.elevate.com/privacyPolicy.html). 

Credit Reference Agencies 

We will use the information stored about you to search the files of one or more credit reference agencies for the purposes of credit assessment or account administration. 

As part of our application process, we will use and search the records of credit reference or fraud prevention agencies to check your identity and to prevent fraud and money laundering. We will also pass information to such agencies to inform them of the performance and repayment history of the loan account and if fraud is suspected or discovered. 

You have the right to receive a copy of your information if you apply to us in writing. A fee (of up to £10.00) will be payable for this service. Please note that we will not provide you with a copy of your credit reference file. 

We will, on request, cooperate with any organisation which we are obliged by law so to do. This may involve passing information about you to them. 

Using your information for marketing purposes 

By submitting information to our website, you are giving us your explicit consent to use your information. Your information might be used to notify you about products and services from us or from other companies which may be of interest to you. We may share your information with them for analysis, for marketing purposes or so that they may contact you about their products or services. 

By providing us with your information, you are giving us your express permission for such companies to contact you by phone, email, SMS or in writing to discuss any product or service including those regulated by the Financial Services Authority (FSA), e.g. mortgages, re-mortgages etc., where an invitation to contact you is required. We may also pass your information to our market research agencies in order to improve the products and services that we offer. 

You have a right **_at any time_** to ask us not to contact you for these purposes. You may send an email to us at [unsubscribe@sunny.co.uk](mailto:unsubscribe@sunny.co.uk) if you wish us to stop. If you opt out of such communications, we will honour such choice once we have had a reasonable opportunity to process your request. We reserve the right to take reasonable steps to authenticate your identity with respect to any such request. 

We reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time by notifying you of the existence and location of the new or revised privacy policy or by posting the changes online at our Website.
